exchangewire.com 2019-09-29

# Privacy Policy | ExchangeWire.com

##### **Visitors to our websites**

When someone visits www.exchangewire.com, we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website (www.exchangewire.com). We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.

#####  **Cookies**

Exchangewire utilises ‘cookies’. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. ExchangeWire uses cookies to keep track of how often you visit our site, and to deliver content specific to your interests. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance – a good guide for all browsers is [here](http://www.lavasoft.com/mylavasoft/securitycenter/blog/configure-your-browser-to-deal-with-cookies). If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our website, including the ability to purchase items. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

#####  **Use of cookies by ExchangeWire**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

In addition to those above some of our ‘share’ functions, such as Facebook Like or Tweet, set cookies for their own purposes. These can vary and are not set explicitly by Exchangewire.com – these too can be blocked by configuring your browser settings.

ExchangeWire collects certain information about your device hardware and software, including, but not limited to:

– IP address  
– Browser type  
– Operating system  
– Access times  
– Referring website addresses  
– Location (down to city level)  
– Device

This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain service quality, and to provide general statistics regarding use of ExchangeWire. If you choose not to have your browser accept cookies, you will still be able to view all of the ExchangeWire site. Google Analytics collects information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from, and the pages they visited. [You can view Google’s privacy policy here](https://policies.google.com/privacy/update).

#####  **Advertising**

ExchangeWire does not deliver personalised advertising across its site. All ads displayed on exchangewire.com are non-personalised, reservation-based ads. The only targeting occurs at a country level.

#####  **Information Sharing**

ExchangeWire does not share any of your personal information with third parties, without your explicit consent.

To opt in to receiving email communications from ExchangeWire, we only require your name and email address as mandatory information.

You can change your mind at any time by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ or ‘update preferences’ link in the footer of any email you receive from us, or by contacting us at info@exchangewire.com.

ExchangeWire uses MailChimp as its marketing automation platform. By opting in to receiving email communications from us, you acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/ "Opens in a new window") and [Terms](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/ "Opens in a new window").

#####  **Security**

Your Exchangewire website user account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. You must always carefully safeguard your user name, password, and any log-in information.

Exchangewire will take reasonable care to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided us with. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third party business partners for whom you have granted permission to contact you will provide sufficient protection of that personal information

#####  **Changes to Privacy Policy**

ExchangeWire may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any substantial changes to this policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the ExchangeWire website, sending you an email, by including an item in the ExchangeWire newsletter, or by any other means reasonably seen to provide you with actual notice.
